Review exercise 110, individual practice. One, indicate that her boyfriend prefers
live plants to cut ones.
Her boyfriend almost never sends her flowers, but he planted a lot in her
garden. Two, indicate that her sisters are attentive to her horticultural needs.
3. Indicate that her boyfriend gives her non-floral presents.
Her boyfriend almost never sends her flowers, but he showers her with other
gifts. 4. Indicate that my boyfriend is good in the flower department.
Her boyfriend almost never sends her flowers, but mine does. 5. Indicate that
it is a true rarity for her boyfriend to send flowers.
Her boyfriend almost never sends her flowers, no matter what. 6. Indicate that
there's actually a slim chance that he might send flowers.
Her boyfriend almost never sends her flowers, but every once in a while he
does. 7. Indicate that her boyfriend remembers to send flowers to his mother.
Her boyfriend almost never sends her flowers, but he never forgets Mother's Day.